madgam.es 2012-12-14

# None

We take privacy very seriously.

Upon authorizing Mad Games, we collect the user's Facebook ID, gender, name, and friends list, and we cache the information in our secure database in order to identify the user and provide a personalized experience in subsequent visits. When the user deauthorizes (removes) the application, all personally identifiable information will be deleted.

_We do not sell or rent the information we collect to any third party._

### Advertisements

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our application. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on our application. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. Similarly, third-party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called "clear gifs" or "beacons") to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the app on which the beacon is located, and to learn which banner ads bring users to a given site.

We do not provide any information to third-party advertising companies. We have no responsibility for the Privacy Policy of third party advertisers, and we would ask you to contact third parties directly if you have any questions.

### Security

We cannot protect, nor does this Privacy Policy apply to, any information that you transmit to other users. You should never transmit personal or identifying information to other users.

### Changes

We may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the email address specified in your social network account and by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to contact [at] app_support@veenx.com
